[
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"10 Matthew Street, Liverpool is the address of which famous venue?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Cavern"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"About Whom Did President Eisenhower Say 'I Just Will Not, I Refuse To Get Into The Gutter With That Guy'", "answer":0, "answers":["Senator Joseph McCarthy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"According To Marilyn Monroe What Was The Only Thing She Wore In Bed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chanel No.5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"After Which Famous Person In History Was The Teddy Bear Named", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"After Whom Is The Teddy Bear Named", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"After Whome is the Teddy Bear Named", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore Roosevelt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Albert Einstein Was Born On The 14 th March 1879 In Germany He Was Educated In Austria And Then Eventually Moved To Switzerland But In Which Country Did He Die", "answer":0, "answers":["America"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"As Of 2000 In Britain John Is Still The Commonest Boys Name What Is The Girls", "answer":0, "answers":["Elizabeth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Allan Stewart Konisburg better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Woody Allan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Allen Konigsberg better known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Woody Allen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Arthur Leech better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cary Grant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Francis Gumm better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Judy Garland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Marion Morrison better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Wayne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Maurice Micklewhite better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Caine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Norma Jean Baker better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Reginald Dwight better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Richard Starkey better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By what name is Robert Zimmerman better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Dylan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By What Name Was William Bonney Better Known As?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy The Kid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"By Which Stage Name Was Norma Jean Baker More Commonly Known", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Can You Name The 4 Stars Of The Goon Show", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Bentine, Peter Sellers, Spike Milligan, Harry Secombe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Complete This partnership Hinge and ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bracket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Dame Shirley Porter Is Heiress To Which Super Market Chain", "answer":0, "answers":["Tesco"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"For what are Allen and Wright most famous?", "answer":0, "answers":["Root beer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"For What Is Peter Roget Famous", "answer":0, "answers":["His Thesaurus Of Words"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"For Which Club Does Paul Merson Now Play", "answer":0, "answers":["Aston Villa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Formerly known as East Pakistan what is this country now called", "answer":0, "answers":["Bangladesh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"How Did Dmaon Hill's Father Graham Die ?", "answer":0, "answers":["In A Plane Crash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"How Did James Dean Die", "answer":0, "answers":["In A Car Crash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"How is Meg Lake better known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mystic Meg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In 1955 Tim Berners Lee Invented something fantasic What was It", "answer":0, "answers":["World Wide Web"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In 1995 Which Comedien Dissapeared For Several Days After Receiving Adverse Reviews", "answer":0, "answers":["Stephen Fry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In 1996 who did The Spice Girls say was their Girl Power role model?", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret Thatcher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In September 2003, Fathers 4 Justice campaigner Jason Hatch caused an embarrassing security breach at Buckingham Palace dressed as who?", "answer":0, "answers":["Batman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which African Country Is The Seaport Of Banana", "answer":0, "answers":["The Democratic Republic Of Congo , Formally Zaire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which Country Was Paper Magnate Robert Maxwell Born ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Czechoslovakia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In which country would you find the original Legoland?", "answer":0, "answers":["Denmark"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In which county is Uttoxeter?", "answer":0, "answers":["Staffordshire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which Couuntry Was The Playwright Tom Stoppard Born", "answer":0, "answers":["Czechoslovakia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In which European country is Dalmatia , from where the Dalmatian Dog gets it's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Croatia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which Ocean Is The Island Group The Maldives", "answer":0, "answers":["Indian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which State Is Fort Knox, The Location Of The USA's Gold Reserves To Be Found?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kentucky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which UK City Was Dick Turpin Hanged?", "answer":0, "answers":["York"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which Us State Is Yosemite National Park", "answer":0, "answers":["California"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Which Us State was John F Kennedy Shot", "answer":0, "answers":["Texas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"In Whose Car Did Mary Jo Kopechne Die At Chappaquidick", "answer":0, "answers":["Edward Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Jane Caine Has A Claim To Fame As The First Person To Do What", "answer":0, "answers":["Speaking Clock Voice"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"King Richard The 1 st Is Sometimes Refered To As What", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard The Lionheart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Name Lloyd Bridges Two Sons ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jeff & Beau"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Name The Playwright Who Was Born On And Who Died On 23rd April", "answer":0, "answers":["Shakespeare"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Name The Worlds Richest Woman ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Queen Elizabeth II"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Name Tthe Australian Actor Who Advertised Fosters Lager On Tv", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Hogan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Of What Were Lee Bowyer & Jonathan Woodgate Of Leads Accused", "answer":0, "answers":["A Racial Assault"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"This Person Voiced The Muppet Characters Fozzie Bear & Kermit The Frog He Also Supplied The Voice To Yoda In The Star Wars Movies What was His Name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Oz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Thomas Hamilton A Former Scout Master Shocked The Nation On 13 th March 1996 But Why", "answer":0, "answers":["Dunblane Massacre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Washington is part of which English city?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sunderland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whaat Do Lord Lucan, Amelia Earheart , & Buster Crabbe Have In Common", "answer":0, "answers":["They All Disappeared Without A Trace"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whaat Is Paddy Ashdown First Name", "answer":0, "answers":["Jeremy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Did Al Capone Die From", "answer":0, "answers":["Syphilis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Did Charles Dawson Appear To Have Found On Piltdown Common", "answer":0, "answers":["The Missing link"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Did Churhill, Cromwell, & Shakespeare Have In Common ?", "answer":0, "answers":["They all Had Red Hair"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Did You Associate With Rod Hull ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Emu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What do Cleopatra, Margarett Thatcher, & Mia Farrow all have in common", "answer":0, "answers":["They All Had Twins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Do Eric Clapton, Marilyn Monroe, And Laarry Grayson All Have In Common", "answer":0, "answers":["They All are Or Were Illegitimate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Do O.J Simpsons Initials Stand For", "answer":0, "answers":["Orenthal James"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Do You Call A Person From Manchester", "answer":0, "answers":["Mancunion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What instrument does Vanessa Mae play", "answer":0, "answers":["Violin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is Andrew Lloyd Webbers Brothers Name ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Julian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is Elton Johns Middle Name", "answer":0, "answers":["Hercules"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is MP Dennis Skinners Nickname ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beast Of Bolsover"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What is Nigel Benn Known Has In The Ring ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Dark Destroyer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is Princess Diana's Madien Name ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spencer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is Ronald Biggs Famous For", "answer":0, "answers":["Being A Great Train Robber"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What is the county town of Cornwall?", "answer":0, "answers":["Truro"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is The Most Common British Surname", "answer":0, "answers":["Smith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What is the nickname of Jamew Gardner, friend of footballer Paul Gascoigne?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five Bellies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is The Only American State That Starts With The Letter 'A' But Doesn't End With The Letter 'A'", "answer":0, "answers":["Arkansas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What is the only country which is crossed by both the Equator and the Tropic Of Cancer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brazil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What is the singer Meat Loafs Real Name", "answer":0, "answers":["Marvin Lee Aday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Is The Title Of Tony Adams Biography", "answer":0, "answers":["Addicted"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Letter Do Most British Names Begin With", "answer":0, "answers":["B"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Nationalaty Was Hans Christian Andersen ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Danish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What nationality was the film legend Greta Garbo, Swedish, German or Polish", "answer":0, "answers":["Swedish"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Part Of Betty Grable Was Insured For Over A Million Dollars", "answer":0, "answers":["Her Legs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Radio Program Did Roy Plomley Dream Up", "answer":0, "answers":["Desert Island Discs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Should You Call An Inhabitaant Of Newcastle", "answer":0, "answers":["A Novocastrian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Surrey town is famed for its salts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Epsom"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was Air Chief Marshall Arthur Harris Called", "answer":0, "answers":["Bomber Harris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was Evonne Cawley's Madien name ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goolangong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was Judge Jefferies Nickname ?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Hanging Judge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What was Madam Tussaud's First name ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was Sir Roger Hollis The Head Of", "answer":0, "answers":["MI5"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What was Spike Milligan's real first name", "answer":0, "answers":["Terence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was The Name Of The Australian Outlaw Who Wore Metal Body Armour", "answer":0, "answers":["Ned Kelly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was The Nickname Of The Assassin Carlos Martinez", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jackal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What Was William Bonney Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy The Kid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"What were the surnames of Bonnie & Clyde", "answer":0, "answers":["Clyde Barrow & Bonnie Parker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where Do Moaris Come From ?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where Do Sinhalese People Come Frome", "answer":0, "answers":["Sri Lanka"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where Is Britain's National Horseracing Museum", "answer":0, "answers":["Newmarket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where is Sir Herbert Baker buried?", "answer":0, "answers":["Westminster Abbey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where is the biggest mosque in the world?", "answer":0, "answers":["Madina, Saudi Arabia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where is the comemoration statue of fictional character Sherlock holems?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baker Street, london"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where Might You Come Across Walloons", "answer":0, "answers":["Belgium"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where was Albert Einstein Born", "answer":0, "answers":["Germany"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where Was Mike Tyson Born", "answer":0, "answers":["Brooklyn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Where would you find the Sea of Tranquility", "answer":0, "answers":["On The Moon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which 'S' is the most populated city in the world?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shanghai"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which 2 People Are Now Best Associated With The Phrase 'You're Fired' (PFE)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Sugar & Donald Trump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Actor Is An International Bridge Player", "answer":0, "answers":["Omar Sharif"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Actor Was Charged With Lewd Behavior In 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Grant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Actor Was Charged With Lewd Behavoir In 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Grant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Actors Real Name Is Morris Micklewhite", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Caine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which actress played the younger Diana Dors in the 1999 TV film The Blonde Bombshell?", "answer":0, "answers":["Keeley Hawes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Actress Was Sued For Not Acting In Boxing Helena", "answer":0, "answers":["Kim Bassinger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which actress was the first wife of Ronald Regan?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Wyman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Argentine Prop Was Sent Off For Knocking Out An English Second Row With A Punch", "answer":0, "answers":["Carlos Mendes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Argentinean General Ordered The Invasion Of The Falkland Islands", "answer":0, "answers":["General Galtieri"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Aussie Wicket Keeper Bet Against His Own Team At 500-1 And Won The Bet", "answer":0, "answers":["Rodney Marsh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Author Had A 'Fatwa' Issued Against Him", "answer":0, "answers":["Salman Rushdie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which aviator was Time magazine's first Man Of The Year in 1927?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles Lindenbergh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Bad Boy Is Arsenals Top Scorer Ever", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Wright"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which British comedian became well known for his broken microphone routine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norman Collier"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which British Director Attempted To Appear In All The Films He Directed", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfred Hitchcock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which British Director Attempted To Appear In All The Films He Directed?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfred Hitchcock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which British Jockey Was Jailed For Tax Evasion", "answer":0, "answers":["Lester Piggot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which British Prime Minister was also the longest serving MP at almost 62 years?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Celebrity Launched A Perfume Range Entitled 'M' Just In Time For Christmas 2007", "answer":0, "answers":["Mariah Carey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which City Is Home To The Little Mermaid Statue", "answer":0, "answers":["Copenhagen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Comedian Is Maried To Caroline Quentin", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Merton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Comedian Wore A Huge Banana Shaped Shoes On Stage In The 1970's", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy Connolly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Controversial Manchester Comedian Died In June 2007 Aged 76", "answer":0, "answers":["Bernard Manning"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which cosmetic magnate died in 2004 at the age of 97?", "answer":0, "answers":["Estee Lauder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Country Owns Easter Island", "answer":0, "answers":["Chile"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Cricketer wenbt by the Name of Beefy", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham (Beefy Botham)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Cricketing Bad Boy Is Known As 'The Cat'", "answer":0, "answers":["Phil Tuffnel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Daughter Of A Lighthouse Keeper Rescued Survivors From A Shipwreck", "answer":0, "answers":["Grace Darling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Engineer's Statue Watches Over The Trains At Paddington Station In London?", "answer":0, "answers":["Isambard Kingdom Brunel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which English comedian's real name is Bob Davies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jasper Carrott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which English County Has The Longest Coastline?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cornwall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which establishments don't have windows or watches?", "answer":0, "answers":["Casino's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which European City Is Famous For Its Latin Quarter", "answer":0, "answers":["Paris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous Actor was Charged with Lewd Behavior in 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Grant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous actress Once Said: ' I am a marvelous housekeeper. Every time I leave a man I keep his house '?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zsa Zsa Gabor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous Artist Painted The Most Paintings", "answer":0, "answers":["Piccaso"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous Child Actor of the 80's is presently giving evidence at the trial of Michael Jackson", "answer":0, "answers":["Corey Feldman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous London Landmark Was Designed by Sir Norman Foster", "answer":0, "answers":["The Millenium Bridge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous Tv Presenters Are Former MP's", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Walden, Robert Kilroy Silk"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Famous Woman Always Carried Pet Owl In Her Pocket ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Florence Nightingale"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which film star's statue stands in Leicester Square, London?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Chaplin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which FootbaIl Bad Boy Was Accused Of Violent Assault Against Tv Presenter Ulrika Jonsson", "answer":0, "answers":["Stan Collymore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Footballer Drop Kicked A Fan At Crystal Palace", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Cantona"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Footballer Famously Slept With Several Miss Worlds Before Leaving Manchester United & Moving To Fulham", "answer":0, "answers":["George Best"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former British Ambassador To The US Is Now BBC's Chief Financial Editor", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Jay"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which former England international footballer was ordered to give his ex-wife over a third of his earnings in a land mark divorce case in 2004?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ray Parlour"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former Goodie Is Into Bird Watching", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Oddie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former Husband And Wife Provide A Link Between The Films Death Becomes Her And Disclosure (PFE)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruce Willis And Demi Moore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former Presenter Of Grandstand Became A Cocaine Addict", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Bough"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former Python Traavlled Round The World", "answer":0, "answers":["Micheal Palin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which former Radio 1 DJ used to broadcast 'Our Tune'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Simon Bates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Former Radio One DJ Used To Broadcast 'Our Tune'", "answer":0, "answers":["Simon Bates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Hollywood Actor Was Taken Into Custody At Sydney Airport In 2006 For Carrying Banned Products Into The Country In his Suitcase?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sylvester Stallone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Hollywood Actress Was Convicted Of Shop Lifting In 2002?", "answer":0, "answers":["Winona Ryder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Hollywood Star Sparked Outraged In 2006 When They He Declared That He Planned To Eat The Placenta Of His Then Unborn Child", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Cruise"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which individual bought one of Leonardo Da Vinci's notebooks for over 19 million pounds in 1994?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Gates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which is the largest of the Canary Islands?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tenerife"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Is The Only US State That Has A Name Ending With Three Vowels?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hawaii"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which James Bond Actor Once Worked As A Coffin Polisher", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which King Had A Dog Named After Him?", "answer":0, "answers":["King Charles ii"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which King Reputedly Tried To Turn Back The Sea ?", "answer":0, "answers":["King Canute"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Labour MP Attempted To Fake His Own Disappearance", "answer":0, "answers":["John Stonehouse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Liberal Leader Was Aquitted Of Attempted Murder", "answer":0, "answers":["Jeremy Thorpe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Manager Clipped A Couple Of Hooligans Ears Round The Ear", "answer":0, "answers":["Brian Clough"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Movies Star Was Famous For The Phrase 'You Dirty Rat''", "answer":0, "answers":["James Cagney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which MP & Former Leader Of The GLC Keeps Salamanders", "answer":0, "answers":["Ken Livingstone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Norwegian explorer's ships included Fram and Maud?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roald Amundsen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Outspoken Ex Mp Shares Her Birthday with Margaret Thatcher", "answer":0, "answers":["Edwina Currie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Politician Is Known As Tarzan", "answer":0, "answers":["Micheal Hestletine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Politician Punched A Protestor Who Threw An Egg At Him During A Visit To Wales In 1991", "answer":0, "answers":["John Prescott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Politician was Nick Named Bambi", "answer":0, "answers":["Tony Blaire"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Pop Stars Called Themselves sharon & Phyllis", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John & Rod Stewart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Presenter Of Tomorrows World Married Keith Chegwin", "answer":0, "answers":["Maggie Philpin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which President Of America Was A Peanut Farmer", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy Carter"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Publisher Was Known As Cap' N Bob", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Maxwell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Romanian Tennis Player Was Famous For His Tantrums", "answer":0, "answers":["Ilie Nastase"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which saint was known as the apostles of Northumbria?", "answer":0, "answers":["St Aidan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which singer won the Eurovision Song Contest in 1999?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlotte Nilsson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which singer wrote the autobiography 'Take It Like A Man'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boy George"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which singer wrote the autobiography 'Take It Like A Man''?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boy George"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Sportsmans Name Was Hurricane", "answer":0, "answers":["Alex Higgins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Supermodel Is Nicknamed 'The Body'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elle McPherson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Television Presenter And Ex-Spurs & England Footballer Became An Alcoholic", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy Greaves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Tennis Player Was Jimmy Connors Engaged To", "answer":0, "answers":["Chirs Evet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Tory Author Won substantial Damages From The Daily Star", "answer":0, "answers":["Jeffrey Archer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Tory MP Made Multiple BT Share Applications", "answer":0, "answers":["Keith Best"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which US University is in the city of Cambridge?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harvard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which writer caused a massive stir in 1926 when she went missing for eleven days?", "answer":0, "answers":["Agatha Christie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Which Zoologist Wrote The Book Man Watching", "answer":0, "answers":["Demond Morris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Batted With An Aluminium Bat", "answer":0, "answers":["Dennis Lillee"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Became Archbishop Of Caterbury in 1980", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Runcie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who became the new Poet Laureate in 1999?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andrew Motion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Bought The Ritz Hotel In Paris In 1979", "answer":0, "answers":["Mohammed Al Fayed"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Broke Into The Queens Bedroom For A Chat", "answer":0, "answers":["Micheal Fagan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Committed Suicide In An Attempt To save Scott's Expedition", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Oates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Did Churchill Refer To As A 'Half Naked Fakir'", "answer":0, "answers":["Mahatma Gandhi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Did Cynthia Powell Marry In 1962?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Lennon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Did John Mcenroe Play 3 Times In Wimbledon Finals", "answer":0, "answers":["Bjorn Borg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Did Princess Anne marry In 1992 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tim lawrence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Famously Said 'You Cannot Be Serious'", "answer":0, "answers":["John McEnroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Founded His Own Production Company Called Ginger Productions?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Evans"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Founded The Playboy Magazine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hugh Hefner"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Founded the Salvation Army ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wiliam Booth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Has The Car Number Plate 'COM1C", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy Tarbuck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who In Music Is Known As The Boss", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruce Springsteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Invented The Electric Light Bulb", "answer":0, "answers":["Thomas Edison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Invented The Minors Lamp ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Humphery Davy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Invented The Potato Crisp In 1853", "answer":0, "answers":["George Crumb"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Actress Betty Joan Perske Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Lauren Bacall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Actress Charlotte Rampling Married To", "answer":0, "answers":["Jean Michelle Jarre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is Ashton Kutcher Famous Older woman wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Demi Moore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is David John Cornwell better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Le Carré"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Gazza", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Gascoigne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is Joley Richardson's famous mother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vanessa Redgrave"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Julie Andrews Married To ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blake Edwards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is Julie Andrews Married To", "answer":0, "answers":["Blake Edwards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Kenneth Brannagh Married To", "answer":0, "answers":["Emma Thompson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is known as 'The Big Yin'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy Connolly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Married To Tatum O' Neil", "answer":0, "answers":["John Mcenroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is Paul Mc-Cartneys Fashion Designer Daughter", "answer":0, "answers":["Stella McCartney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is Stevland Morris Hardaway Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Stevie Wonder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who is Stevland Morris Hardaway better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stevie Wonder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is The Heaviest Member Ever To Have Sat In Parliment", "answer":0, "answers":["Cyril Smith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Is The Sister Of Warren Beatty ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shirley Mclaine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Made A Controversioal Speach Concerning 'Rivers Of Blood'", "answer":0, "answers":["Enoch Powell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Nickname is Beefy ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Once Said Of The Navy 'It's Only Traditions Were Rum, Sodomy & The Lash'", "answer":0, "answers":["Winston Churchill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Or What Is The Actress Uma Thurman Named After", "answer":0, "answers":["A Hindu Goddess"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Replaced Betty Boothroyd As Speaker Of The House Of Commons", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Martin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Resigned After His Affair With Christine Keeler", "answer":0, "answers":["John Profumo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who sacked Jonathon Shallit as her manager in 2000?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlotte Church"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Said 'I Hope Harry Secombe Goes Before Me, I Don't Want Him Singing At My Funeral'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spike Milligan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Said 'We Have Become A Grandmother' In 1989", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret Thatcher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Said Of Touring Pakistan 'I Wouldn't Even Send My Mother In Law There'", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Botham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Spent A Year In Prison For Sleeping With An Underage Girl", "answer":0, "answers":["Graham Rix"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Sued For Libel After Being Described As Boring", "answer":0, "answers":["William Roache (Ken Barlow)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Assassinated By Two Sikh Bodyguards", "answer":0, "answers":["Indiri Gandhi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was At The Centre Of Englands Match Fixing Scandal", "answer":0, "answers":["Hansie Cronje"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Banned In Germany, Italy & The USSR In The 1930's", "answer":0, "answers":["Mickey Mouse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Born And Also Died During Halley's Comet Passing ?", "answer":0, "answers":["MArk Twain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was Born Farouk Bulsara?", "answer":0, "answers":["Freddie Mercury"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Caught On Film Kissing The Duchess Of Yorks Toes", "answer":0, "answers":["John Bryan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was elected as MP for Belfast West in 1997?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gerry Adams"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was elected as the Conservative MP for Henley in 2001?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Elvis Presleys Manager", "answer":0, "answers":["Colonel Tom Parker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Eric Sykes On Screen Sister", "answer":0, "answers":["Hattie Jaques"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Faamous For Her 'Pomes'", "answer":0, "answers":["Pam Ayers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was famously convicted of horse stealing at York Assizes in 1739 and subsequently hanged?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dick Turpin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Famously Quoted As Saying 'The Only Thing She Wears In Bed Is Channel No.5'", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was French President From 1969 Until 1974", "answer":0, "answers":["Georges Pompidou"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Humphrey Bogarts 4th Wife ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lauren Bacall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Killed By Indians At Little Big Horn", "answer":0, "answers":["General Custer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Known As Scarface", "answer":0, "answers":["Al Capone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was known as the 'Maid Of Orleans'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joan Of Arc"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Known As The Face That Launched A Thousand Ships 'Helen Of Troy'", "answer":0, "answers":["Helen Of Troy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Known As The Forces Sweetheart", "answer":0, "answers":["Dame Vera Lynn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Known As The Maid Of Orleans", "answer":0, "answers":["Joan Of Arc"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Known As The Old Groaner", "answer":0, "answers":["Bing Crosby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Maradona Playing For When He Was First Caught Taking Cocaine", "answer":0, "answers":["Napoli"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Married To Robin Givens until 1989", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Tyson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was Sent Off In Both Opening Premiership Games Of The 2000 Season", "answer":0, "answers":["Patrick Vieira"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The 16th Century Seer Famous For His Predictions", "answer":0, "answers":["Nostradamus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Archbishop Of Canterbury In 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["George Carey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Director General Of The BBC In 1995", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord Reith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was the Director of the C.I.A during 1976-77 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Bush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First American Chess Champion ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Fischer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First Director General Of The BBC", "answer":0, "answers":["Marmaduke Hussey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First Ever Man Seen On Channel 4?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Whitely"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was the first ever president of the united states", "answer":0, "answers":["John Hanson (1715 - 1783)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was The First Man To Run A Mile In Under 4 Minutes", "answer":0, "answers":["Roger Bannister"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First man To Set Foot On The Moon ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Neil Armstrong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was the first member of the Royal Family to graduate from University?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prince Charles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First Player To Be Sent Off In An FA Cup Final", "answer":0, "answers":["Moran"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was the first snooker player to be a subject of this is your life on the 14 th January 1978?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ray Reardon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was the First Woman To Be Officially Ranked A Billionaire In The USA?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oprah Winfrey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The First Woman To Fly Solo Accross The Atlantic ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amelia Earheart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Joan Collins Fan Club", "answer":0, "answers":["Julian Clarey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Joan Collins Fan Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Julian Clarey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Last English Player To Be Sent Off In The World Cup (2006)", "answer":0, "answers":["Wayne Rooney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was The Naked Chef", "answer":0, "answers":["Jamie Oliver"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who was The Second Man To Set Foot On The Moon", "answer":0, "answers":["Buzz Aldrin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Young German Who Landed His Plane In Red Square ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mathias Rust"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was The Youngest US President To Die In Office", "answer":0, "answers":["John F Kennedy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Was William Bonney Better Known As", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy The Kid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who won a place in the Guinness Book of Records for writing 26 books in 1983?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barbara Cartland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Would You Associate With Lou Costello", "answer":0, "answers":["Bud Abbott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Wrote A Diary About Her Attempts To Avoid The Nazi's", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Frank"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who Wrote A personal cheque for $23,000,000 when buying RKO ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Howard Hughes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Who wrote the book 'The Guns Of Navarone''", "answer":0, "answers":["Alistair McClaine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whom did Mervyn King replace as Governer of the Bank of England in 2003?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eddie George"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whom Did Neil Kinnock Succeed As Leader Of The Labour Party?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Foot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Catchphraase Is 'Nice To See You To See You Nice'", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruce Forsythe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Catchphrase Was 'Here's Another Fine Mess You've Gotten Me Into'", "answer":0, "answers":["Oliver Hardy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Children Are Trixiebell, Little pixie, & Peaches", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Geldof & Paula Yates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Daughter Married Thin Lizzys Phil Lynott", "answer":0, "answers":["Leslie Crowther"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Ear Did Mike Tyson Bite Off", "answer":0, "answers":["Evander Holyfield"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose final film as director was Eyes Wide Shut?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Kubrick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Last Words Were Reputedly, 'ET TU BRUTE' ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Julius Caesar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Nickname Was Satchmo", "answer":0, "answers":["Louis Armstrong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Real Name Is 'Arthur Stanley Jefferson'", "answer":0, "answers":["Stan Laurel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Real Name Is 'Cherilyn Sarkisian La Pierre'", "answer":0, "answers":["Cher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Real Name Is 'Gordon Sumner'", "answer":0, "answers":["Sting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Real Name Is 'Paul Hewson'", "answer":0, "answers":["Bono"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose Real Name Is Eric Clap ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Clapton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Whose son got lost in the desert during the Paris Daker rally ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mrs Thathchers Son Mark"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"Why Did Michael Fagan Hit The Headlines In 1982", "answer":0, "answers":["Broke Into Queens Bedroom"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"PEOPLE_AND_PLACES", "lang":"en", "tags":["PEOPLE_AND_PLACES"], "question":"With Whome Do You Associate Lady Falkender", "answer":0, "answers":["Harold Wilson"], "source":""}
]
